A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- Minute books and ledgers, 1849-1952
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures (623), March 1918-February 1920 (Volume 445)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures (624), December 1919-March 1923 (Volume 446)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures (625), January 1920-December 1925 (Volume 447)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures (626), May 1924-December 1925 (Volume 448)
  - [There is no volume 449] (Volume 449)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures index (627), n. d. (Volume 450)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, cash book (586), 1909-1918 (Volume 451)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, cash book (599), 1909-1918 (Volume 452)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, cash book (597), 1921-1924 (Volume 453)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, classification of construction and equipment (632), 1909-1911 (Volume 454)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, construction detail (629), 1911-1912 (Volume 455)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, financial reports (657), 1909-1910 (Volume 456)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, financial reports (658), 1911 (Volume 457)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, financial reports (659), 1912 (Volume 458)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, fixed capital by primary accounts (634), 1915-1919 (Volume 459)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, general balance sheets and comparative income and expense statements (661), 1917-1920 (Volume 460)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, general balance sheets (652), July 1920-December 1921 (Volume 461)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, general balance sheets and statistical data (653), 1922 (Volume 462)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, general ledger (565), 1923-1925 (Volume 462a)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (568), 1910-1912 (Volume 463)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (570), 1912 (Volume 464)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (571), 1912-1913 (Volume 465)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (572), 1913 (Volume 466)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (573), 1913-1914 (Volume 467)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (574), 1914-1915 (Volume 468)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (577), 1916-1917 (Volume 469)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (582), 1922-1923 (Volume 470)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (583), 1923-1924 (Volume 471)
  - [There is no volume 472] (Volume 472)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal (584), 1924-1925 (Volume 473)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, journal of New York office (585), 1911-1922 (Volume 474)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, ledger (576), 1916 (Volume 475)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, ledger (578), 1917-1918 (Volume 476)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, ledger (566), 1909-1918 (Volume 477)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, ledger (563), 1917-1920 (Volume 478)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, ledger (564), 1920-1922 (Volume 479)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (678), 30 June 1909-26 July 1909 (Volume 480)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (679), November 1909-June 1911 (Volume 481)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (680), July 1911-April 1913 (Volume 482)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (681), May 1913-December 1914 (Volume 483)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (682), January 1915-December 1915 (Volume 484)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (683), January-December 1916 (Volume 485)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (684), January-December 1917 (Volume 486)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (685), February-December 1918 (Volume 487)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (686), January-December 1919 (Volume 488)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (687), January-December 1920 (Volume 489)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, minute book (688), January 1921-April 1923 (Volume 490)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484a), 1913-1917 (Volume 491)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484b), 1914-1925 (Volume 491a)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484c), 1904-1912 (Volume 491b)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484d), 1913-1915 (Volume 491c)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484e), 1916-1919 (Volume 491d)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, Relief Association minute book (484f), 1920-1925 (Volume 492)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, taxes-prepaid and accrued (640), 1918-1923 (Volume 492a)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, voucher register (601), 1909-June 1911 (Volume 492b)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, voucher register (602), 1911 (Volume 493)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Co., etc., stocks and bonds ledger (560), 1911-1912 (Volume 508)
  - Virginia Transportation Company, minute book (691), 1908-1912 (Volume 494)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, field cost ledger (59H5-1), 1917-1920 (Volume 495)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, minutes (59J-1), 1913-1915 (Volume 495a)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, minutes (59J-2), 1915-1918 (Volume 495b)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, minutes (59J-3), 1918-1921 (Volume 495c)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, minutes (59J-4), 1921-1923 (Volume 495d)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, minutes (59J-5), 1923-1926 (Volume 495e)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, stock ledger (59K-2), 1919-1926 (Volume 496)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, stock ledger (59K-3), 1921-1926 (Volume 497)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, stock ledger (59K-4), 1923-1926 (Volume 498)
  - Virginia Western Power Company, stock transfer journal (59L-4), n. d. (Volume 499)
  - Westhampton Park Railway Company, journal (693), 1901-1902 (Volume 500)
  - Westhampton Park Railway Company, minute book (694-695), 1900-1902 (Volume 501-502)
  - William Northrop and T. Wickham, receivers' inventory (558), 1905-1908 (Volume 503)
  - William Northrop and T. Wickham, receivers' journal (531), 1904-1905 (Volume 504)
  - William Northrop and T. Wickham, summary of equipment (558A), 1905-1909 (Volume 505)
  - William Northrop and T. Wickham, trial balance (557), 1904-1909 (Volume 506)
  - Willoughby Bay Traction Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (696), 1905-1906 (Volume 507)